Good morning to you who have just been evicted.
It's true that we came to see the shed today,
Worst you can do in your life is invest in other people's land.
And it's been The Ruin of Many of War Wars.
I'll leave it up there,
I'll go try to unwind the car there.
The shed is not mine.
The guys gave me the best.
It's been a few days already.
There's a person who's on the right track there and he's in good spirits.
I'm going to get the chevas now.
You know,
I'm going to ride there again.
I think he's jealous,
he's on.
You need to keep celebrating too,
right?
Mano,
there are only 49 days left to set up a business and then we go,
mano 1 Chevette deep down there mano we see to Dar certain mano,
for God's sake,
it's not possible,
Cara
caraca bro what do i do
the car doesn't start bro i don't know what i do bro it's not rolling,
old man.
I needed the car to work,
to sleep,
to do a lot of things.
Brother.
I'm going to play some parts of this video today,
bro things aren't flowing.
Time is passing,
oh the time that I'm on foot again,
truffle on foot,
rain,
no car,
no place to sleep.
And that's it,
bro.
I know, man,
I don't know what I do,
are you on?